---
profiles:
    searchnode:
        label: "Search Server"
        prefix: "search"
        allow_suffix: true
        primary_role: "SEARCH"
        pool: "SEARCH_POOL"
        secondary_role: "MASTER"
        requires_primary_role: false
        requires_secondary_role: true
        requires_pool: false
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-db-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["search"]
    databasenode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-db-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["database"]
        label: "Database Server"
        prefix: "db"
        primary_role: "DATABASE"
        requires_pool: false
        allowed_classes:
          - io_class
          - database_class
    devnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web"
        label: "Dev Machine"
        vlans: ["service"]
        prefix: "dev"
        allow_suffix: true
        primary_role: "DEVEL"
        pool: "DEVEL"
    webnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web"
        label: "Web Server"
        prefix: "web"
        requires_secondary_role: true
    funcnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-queue-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["search"]
        label: "Func Overlord"
        prefix: "func"
        primary_role: "WEBOPS"
        pool: "UTIL"
    puppetnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-queue-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["search"]
        label: "Puppet Master"
        prefix: "puppet"
        primary_role: "WEBOPS"
        pool: "PUPPETEERS"
    webappnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["search"]
        label: "Web Server v2"
        prefix: "web-v2"
        requires_secondary_role: true
        primary_role: "TUMBLR_APP"
        secondary_role: "ALL"
    adminwebnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        label: "Admin Web Server"
        prefix: "adminweb"
        primary_role: "TUMBLR_APP"
        pool: "ADMIN_POOL"
        secondary_role: "ALL"
    assetnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web"
        label: "Asset Server"
        prefix: "assets"
        requires_secondary_role: false
    regionservernode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-hadoop-v2"
        label: "Hbase Region Server"
        prefix: "hbrs"
        vlans: ["hadoop"]
        allow_suffix: true
        primary_role: "HADOOP"
        secondary_role: "REGION_SERVER"
    hbasemasternode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-queue-v2"
        label: "Hbase Master Server"
        vlans: ["hadoop"]
        prefix: "hbm"
        allow_suffix: true
        primary_role: "HADOOP"
        secondary_role: "HBASE_MASTER"
    namenode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-queue-v2"
        label: "Hadoop NameNode"
        vlans: ["hadoop"]
        prefix: "nn"
        allow_suffix: true
        primary_role: "HADOOP"
        secondary_role: "NAMENODE"
    appcronnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web"
        label: "App Cron Server"
        prefix: "app-cron"
        primary_role: "TUMBLR_APP"
        pool: "UTIL"
    servicenode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        label: "Platform Service Server"
        prefix: "service"
        allow_suffix: true
        primary_role: "SERVICE"
    bastionnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        label: "Bastion Server"
        prefix: "bastion"
        primary_role: "BASTION"
        vlans: ["bastion"]
        operating_system: "centos_5"
    reponode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["search"]
        label: "Repo Server"
        prefix: "repo"
        primary_role: "INFRA"
    sreutilnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web"
        label: "Utility Server"
        prefix: "util"
        allow_suffix: true
        primary_role: "UTILITY"
        pool: "UTIL"
    perimeternode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        operating_system: ["centos_5"]
        label: "Perimeter Server"
        vlans: ["search"]
        prefix: "p"
        allow_suffix: true
    varnishnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        operating_system: ["centos_5"]
        label: "Varnish Server"
        vlans: ["search"]
        prefix: "v"
        allow_suffix: true
        primary_role: "SERVICE"
    memcachenode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        label: "Memcached Server"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["service"]
        prefix: "memcache"
        allow_suffix: true
        primary_role: "CACHE"
    gearmannode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-queue-v2"
        label: "Gearmand Server"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["service"]
        prefix: "gm"
        primary_role: "TUMBLR_APP"
        pool: "GEARMAN_POOL"
    gobnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web"
        label: "Gob Server"
        prefix: "tinyurl"
        primary_role: "SERVICE"
        secondary_role: "Gob"
    aaacanode:
        cobbler_profile: "sl-6.2-x86_64-web-v2"
        label: "AAA/CA Server"
        prefix: "aaa"
        vlans: ["aaa"]
        primary_role: "INFRA"
        allow_suffix: true
        attributes:
          super_important_tag: true
          lower_case_attribute: Hello world
          numeric_attribute: 123
          nodeclass: shouldnt be set to this
        clear_attributes:
          - nodeclass
          - delete_me
          - super_dangerous_tag
    dhcpnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        label: "DHCP/iPXE Server"
        prefix: "dhcp"
        vlans: ["provisioning"]
        primary_role: "INFRA"
        allow_suffix: false
    mailrelaynode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        label: "Mail Relay Server"
        prefix: "mx"
        vlans: ["mail"]
        primary_role: "MAIL"
        pool: "MAILRELAY_POOL"
        allow_suffix: false
    mrepotestnode:
        cobbler_profile: "CentOS-5.6-x86_64-web-mrepo-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["search"]
        label: "Mrepo Test Client"
        prefix: "testmrepo"
        primary_role: "DEVEL"
    scribecentralnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-scribe"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["search"]
        label: "Scribe Central Server"
        prefix: "scribe"
        primary_role: "TUMBLR_APP"
        pool: "SCRIBE_POOL"
        secondary_role: "ALL"
    monitornode:
        cobbler_profile: "sl-6.2-x86_64-web-v2"
        operating_system: "sl_6"
        vlans: ["monitoring"]
        label: "Monitor Node"
        prefix: "monitor"
        primary_role: "MONITOR"
        allow_suffix: true
    icinganode:
        cobbler_profile: "sl-6.2-x86_64-web-v2"
        operating_system: "sl_6"
        vlans: ["monitoring"]
        label: "Icinga Node"
        prefix: "icinga"
        primary_role: "ICINGA"
        allow_suffix: true
    lognode:
        cobbler_profile: "sl-6.2-x86_64-web-v2"
        operating_system: "sl_6"
        vlans: ["logging"]
        label: "Log Node"
        prefix: "rsyslog"
        primary_role: "RSYSLOG"
        allow_suffix: true
    scribeserver:
        cobbler_profile: "sl-6.2-x86_64-web-v2"
        operating_system: "sl_6"
        vlans: ["service"]
        label: "Scribe Server"
        prefix: "scribe"
        primary_role: "SCRIBE"
        allow_suffix: true
    collinsnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["provisioning"]
        label: "Collins Server"
        prefix: "collins"
        primary_role: "UTIL"
        allow_suffix: false
    gitcachenode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["service"]
        label: "Git Cache"
        prefix: "gitcache"
        primary_role: "GIT_CACHE"
        allow_suffix: false
    redisnode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-queue-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["service"]
        label: "Redis Server"
        prefix: "redis"
        primary_role: "CACHE"
        secondary_role: "REDIS"
        allow_suffix: true
    datanode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-hadoop-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["hadoop"]
        label: "Hadoop Datanode"
        prefix: "dn"
        primary_role: "HADOOP"
        secondary_role: "DATANODE"
        allow_suffix: true
    mrepobuildernode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["search"]
        label: "Mrepo Build Server"
        prefix: "mrepo"
        primary_role: "REPO"
        pool: "MREPO_POOL"
        secondary_role: "MREPO_BUILDER"
        allow_suffix: false
    mrepomirrornode:
        cobbler_profile: "centos-5.6-x86_64-web-v2"
        operating_system: "centos_5"
        vlans: ["search"]
        label: "Mrepo Mirror Server"
        prefix: "mrepo"
        primary_role: "REPO"
        pool: "MREPO_POOL"
        secondary_role: "MREPO_MIRROR"
        allow_suffix: false
    testattributesnode:
        label: "Test Custom Attributes Node"
        prefix: "test"
        vlans: ["whatever"]
        primary_role: "PRI_ROLE"
        requires_pool: no
        allow_suffix: true
        attributes:
          super_important_tag: true
          lower_case_attribute: Hello world
          numeric_attribute: 123
          nodeclass: shouldnt be set to this
        clear_attributes:
          - nodeclass
          - delete_me
          - duplicate_attribute
          - super_dangerous_tag
          - duplicate_attribute
